# Luca Liebenberg

Cape Town, Western Cape, South Africa



liebenbergluca@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/luca-liebenberg

# Summary

I am currently at the Cape Town Creative Academy, where I am studying Interaction Design & Front-End Development. I am in my 3rd and final year.

I am a continuous learner, who is pursuing to look for internships with UX/UI, Software and Blockchain companies until my graduation, hoping to learn as much as I can and obtain industry work experience.

GitHub: https://github.com/lucaliebenberg

Portfolio: lucaliebenberg.com

# **Experience**



### **Blockchain Developer**

**Brainnest** 

Jan 2023 - Present (1 month)

Creating a private network and installing the chain's distributed ledger

Skills: • Blockchain • Smart Contracts • Solidity • Ripple • Ethereum • Factom • C++ • JavaScript

# **User Experience Designer**

**TILATA** 

Dec 2022 - Present (2 months)

Skills: • User Experience Design • User Interface Design • Communication • Problem Solving • Figma



#### Junior Web Developer

Freelance

Jun 2022 - Present (8 months)

Skills: • HTML • CSS • Bootstrap 5 • JavaScript • React.js • Netlify • Git • Github



### User Experience Designer

Polymorph Systems

Dec 2022 - Jan 2023 (2 months)

Skills: • User Experience Design • User Interface Design • Design Sprints • Prototyping • User Testing •

Problem Solving • Figma • Miro • Frontend Development (Angular) • Github • Git



#### Delivery Driver

Pizza Fair Constantia

Nov 2021 - Dec 2022 (1 year 2 months)

# Frontend Developer

**Code Capsules** 

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022 (2 months)

Skills: • HTML • Bootstrap 5 • React.js • Next.js • Git • Github

#### **Education**



Design & Development, Bachelor of Arts - Interaction Design

2021 - 2023

Front End Development, Product Design/Interaction Design, Business Management, Market Research, Design Thinking and Animation

# **Bishops Diocesan College**

NSC, Music, Economics and Biology Jan 2015 - Nov 2019

# Llandovery College

Exchange, General Studies Jun 2017 - Sep 2017

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

- (A) Legacy Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp
- (A) JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures freeCodeCamp
- Foundations of Decentralized Finance (DeFi) LinkedIn
- in Introduction to NFTs: Non-fungible Tokens LinkedIn
- in Blockchain and Smart Contracts Security LinkedIn
- in Blockchain Basics LinkedIn
- Building an Ethereum Blockchain App: 1 Introduction to Blockchain LinkedIn
- Building an Ethereum Blockchain App: 2 Introduction to Ethereum LinkedIn

- in Building an Ethereum Blockchain App: 3 Ethereum Development LinkedIn
- Building an Ethereum Blockchain App: 4 Ethereum Development Tools LinkedIn
- Building an Ethereum Blockchain App: 5 Your Ethereum Wallet LinkedIn
- Building an Ethereum Blockchain App: 6 Building Your First Ethereum App LinkedIn
- in Building an Ethereum Blockchain App: 7 Smart Contracts LinkedIn
- Building an Ethereum Blockchain App: 8 Supply Chain Smart Contract dApp LinkedIn
- in Bootstrap 5 Essential Training LinkedIn
- in React: Working with APIs LinkedIn
- in Learning Next.js LinkedIn
- in React.js Essential Training LinkedIn
- Building an Ethereum Blockchain App: 9 Testing Ethereum Apps LinkedIn
- in Blockchain: Beyond the Basics LinkedIn
- in Blockchain: Learning Solidity LinkedIn
- in Cryptocurrency Foundations LinkedIn
- in Securing Cryptocurrencies LinkedIn
- Building an Ethereum Blockchain App: 10 Deployment and Maintenance LinkedIn
- in Building an Ethereum Blockchain App: 11 Integrating Non-Blockchain Apps LinkedIn

- in Blockchain for Developers: Hyperledger Fabric on Azure LinkedIn
- React.js: Building an Interface LinkedIn
- in Swift 5 Essential Training LinkedIn
- in Become a Blockchain Developer LinkedIn
- Advance Your Skills in the Blockchain LinkedIn
- in Blockchain Programming in iOS Using Swift LinkedIn
- in Build an Ethereum Blockchain App LinkedIn
- in Building Web3 Decentralized Apps in Ethereum LinkedIn
- in React Hooks LinkedIn
- in GitHub Quick Tips LinkedIn
- in TypeScript Essential Training LinkedIn
- React: Using TypeScript LinkedIn

#### Skills

JavaScript • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • HTML • React.js • HTML5 • Git • Figma (Software) • GitHub • Problem Solving • Smart Contracts